[{"answer": "You're not kidding.", "docId": "120315pmt", "aSentId": 41, "question": "\"Viva Rock Vegas\"?", "qSentId": 40}, {"answer": "That's exactly right.", "docId": "120315pmt", "aSentId": 46, "question": "Blu-Ray?", "qSentId": 45}, {"answer": "No, it's not on the card.", "docId": "120315pmt", "aSentId": 53, "question": "That's on the card, right?", "qSentId": 52}, {"answer": "I didn't start until about three and a half years ago.", "docId": "120315pmt", "aSentId": 72, "question": "But you never did stand-up?", "qSentId": 71}, {"answer": "I do colleges.", "docId": "120315pmt", "aSentId": 89, "question": "What do you do?", "qSentId": 88}, {"answer": "I don't.", "docId": "120315pmt", "aSentId": 101, "question": "Do you still do it?", "qSentId": 100}, {"answer": "'DONNELL: You know, actually I went back about three years ago.", "docId": "120315pmt", "aSentId": 103, "question": "Would you do it ever again?", "qSentId": 102}, {"answer": "There are three.", "docId": "120315pmt", "aSentId": 126, "question": "How many kids in your family?", "qSentId": 125}, {"answer": "CHALE: My dad was the dean of students at the Loyola Center, Rome campus, for Chicago, Illinois -- Chicago, Loyola Chicago.", "docId": "120315pmt", "aSentId": 147, "question": "You were born in Rome, Italy?", "qSentId": 146}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "120315pmt", "aSentId": 166, "question": "And were you Oliver?", "qSentId": 165}, {"answer": "Well, it was a kids' production, so they would take just about anything.", "docId": "120315pmt", "aSentId": 180, "question": "And you enjoy singing, I take it, if that was a musical production?", "qSentId": 179}, {"answer": "I played a lot of sports.", "docId": "120315pmt", "aSentId": 183, "question": "And in high school, you were athletic, I take it?", "qSentId": 182}, {"answer": "Yes, OK.", "docId": "120315pmt", "aSentId": 191, "question": "The singers, FOX?", "qSentId": 190}, {"answer": "Yes, not well.", "docId": "120315pmt", "aSentId": 196, "question": "In college, as well?", "qSentId": 195}, {"answer": "I didn't hear that.", "docId": "120315pmt", "aSentId": 237, "question": "You didn't?", "qSentId": 236}, {"answer": "She tweeted me that she was going to watch the -- she was going to go on a date.", "docId": "120315pmt", "aSentId": 242, "question": "Didn't you tweet something?", "qSentId": 241}, {"answer": "We thought, actually, that was too many days, when we told the joke.", "docId": "120315pmt", "aSentId": 270, "question": "How did you do that?", "qSentId": 269}, {"answer": "No, because she's really nice and charismatic.", "docId": "120315pmt", "aSentId": 276, "question": "And is it awkward and weird?", "qSentId": 275}, {"answer": "He's right here.", "docId": "120315pmt", "aSentId": 288, "question": "Ryan Seacrest?", "qSentId": 287}, {"answer": "We are friendly.", "docId": "120315pmt", "aSentId": 291, "question": "But you're actually friendly with him, yes?", "qSentId": 290}, {"answer": "Without exception, no one has said you're going down.", "docId": "120315pmt", "aSentId": 302, "question": "Has anyone ever become very angry and contacted you?", "qSentId": 301}, {"answer": "No matter how badly we make fun of them.", "docId": "120315pmt", "aSentId": 306, "question": "As often as possible?", "qSentId": 305}, {"answer": "Bless you.", "docId": "120315pmt", "aSentId": 338, "question": "I was one of the legion of fans that was saying what happened?", "qSentId": 337}, {"answer": "Sometimes it does.", "docId": "120315pmt", "aSentId": 369, "question": "Can we put -- well, no, it said something like -- doesn't it say things about the person as they're down there?", "qSentId": 368}, {"answer": "I sort of feel like -- no, like doesn't like ice in his drinks.", "docId": "120315pmt", "aSentId": 372, "question": "Stud muffin?", "qSentId": 371}, {"answer": "-- citrus fruit.", "docId": "120315pmt", "aSentId": 378, "question": "Sore gums?", "qSentId": 377}, {"answer": "Oh, it was a -- I was OK with it.", "docId": "120315pmt", "aSentId": 408, "question": "That's just a happy day, right?", "qSentId": 407}, {"answer": "I -- my wife is way more even keel.", "docId": "120315pmt", "aSentId": 419, "question": "What kind of a dad are you, strict?", "qSentId": 418}, {"answer": "And well, I mean I gave the kid cigarettes just a few years ago, because I'm like I don't even want to start on this.", "docId": "120315pmt", "aSentId": 430, "question": "And where did you meet?", "qSentId": 429}, {"answer": "Oh, it's so hard, Rosie.", "docId": "120315pmt", "aSentId": 440, "question": "Has fame affected your ability to be out in public with your family?", "qSentId": 439}, {"answer": "It's not -- it's not bad.", "docId": "120315pmt", "aSentId": 454, "question": "Not at all?", "qSentId": 453}, {"answer": "Every man and woman, I will French kiss, for all that.", "docId": "120315pmt", "aSentId": 483, "question": "And didn't you promise to French kiss every man and woman who participated?", "qSentId": 482}, {"answer": "Wow.", "docId": "120315pmt", "aSentId": 499, "question": "Who did you look up to and go, hey, that's the person I'd like to be like?", "qSentId": 498}, {"answer": "Well, I did it -- yes, I'm totally.", "docId": "120315pmt", "aSentId": 512, "question": "Now have you ever met any one of these people and then been star struck?", "qSentId": 511}, {"answer": "He was that and more so.", "docId": "120315pmt", "aSentId": 519, "question": "And was he as you had imagined?", "qSentId": 518}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "120315pmt", "aSentId": 531, "question": "Are your kids funny?", "qSentId": 530}, {"answer": "It's pretty great.", "docId": "120315pmt", "aSentId": 548, "question": "He does?", "qSentId": 547}, {"answer": "And I love it.", "docId": "120315pmt", "aSentId": 555, "question": "Four?", "qSentId": 554}, {"answer": "Well --", "docId": "120315pmt", "aSentId": 560, "question": "'DONNELL: You would?", "qSentId": 559}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "120315pmt", "aSentId": 570, "question": "Really?", "qSentId": 569}, {"answer": "A legend.", "docId": "120315pmt", "aSentId": 590, "question": "Come on, is she amazing?", "qSentId": 589}, {"answer": "No, I thought it was hysterical.", "docId": "120315pmt", "aSentId": 605, "question": "Were you ever mad?", "qSentId": 604}, {"answer": "Let's hope it does well.", "docId": "120315pmt", "aSentId": 618, "question": "Watch \"Community,\" will you?", "qSentId": 617}, {"answer": "I'm staying for that.", "docId": "120315pmt", "aSentId": 623, "question": "Please stay, will you?", "qSentId": 622}, {"answer": "I'm great, Rosie.", "docId": "120315pmt", "aSentId": 634, "question": "Anjelica, how are you?", "qSentId": 633}, {"answer": "It's fantastic.", "docId": "120315pmt", "aSentId": 637, "question": "How perfect is the show?", "qSentId": 636}, {"answer": "It is.", "docId": "120315pmt", "aSentId": 644, "question": "This is the first time that you've done series TV, yes?", "qSentId": 643}, {"answer": "We are.", "docId": "120315pmt", "aSentId": 649, "question": "Are we going to get to see Ilene sing finally?", "qSentId": 648}, {"answer": "Totally nerve racking but we have two amazing composers on the series, Scott Wittman and Marc Shaiman and they got me through it.", "docId": "120315pmt", "aSentId": 653, "question": "Was it nerve racking when you had to do that?", "qSentId": 652}, {"answer": "And actually -- god, what was it called, our tango, Raul's and my tango and --", "docId": "120315pmt", "aSentId": 657, "question": "Right?", "qSentId": 656}, {"answer": "USTON: Yes.", "docId": "120315pmt", "aSentId": 659, "question": "In the \"Addams Family\"?", "qSentId": 658}, {"answer": "Well, first of all, the writing on the series was so good.", "docId": "120315pmt", "aSentId": 668, "question": "Well, when they asked you to do this, what made you consider coming to New York and doing series TV?", "qSentId": 667}, {"answer": "That's right.", "docId": "120315pmt", "aSentId": 688, "question": "So your husband Robert who everyone loved, tremendous artist and he passed away about three years ago now?", "qSentId": 687}, {"answer": "It was.", "docId": "120315pmt", "aSentId": 691, "question": "And that must have been very difficult to imagine how to move forward?", "qSentId": 690}, {"answer": "She sings a little something her grandfather used to sing.", "docId": "120315pmt", "aSentId": 804, "question": "Does she sing a ballad when she gets to sing?", "qSentId": 803}, {"answer": "I have a baby book that I started writing in as soon as I could kind of spell in which I -- I say I want to be an actress.", "docId": "120315pmt", "aSentId": 807, "question": "Did you feel pushed or drawn or pulled?", "qSentId": 806}, {"answer": "No, but there's something about really good material that you feel like a squirrel with a nut in your cheek, you know.", "docId": "120315pmt", "aSentId": 830, "question": "Did you -- anyone say to you this has Oscar potential?", "qSentId": 829}, {"answer": "Well, yeah.", "docId": "120315pmt", "aSentId": 845, "question": "do you want to do it?", "qSentId": 844}, {"answer": "On \"The Oriental.\"", "docId": "120315pmt", "aSentId": 853, "question": "Do you remember winning?", "qSentId": 852}, {"answer": "He was happy.", "docId": "120315pmt", "aSentId": 869, "question": "What did your dad say to you after you won, do you remember?", "qSentId": 868}, {"answer": "You aren't tough enough.", "docId": "120315pmt", "aSentId": 895, "question": "How come?", "qSentId": 894}, {"answer": "Unbelievable.", "docId": "120315pmt", "aSentId": 911, "question": "What has happened that we are fighting again for reproductive rights in America?", "qSentId": 910}]